articledominance.com 2018-08-29

# Privacy

This privacy policy explains how bearlike.com (we, us, our) collect and use your personal information. We value your privacy so please take a few minutes to read and understand our privacy policy.

**Types of information we collect**

We collect personally and non-personally identifiable information from you. The former may include but is not limited to your name, email address, location, age, and gender. Non-personally identifiable information may include internet protocol (IP) address, internet service provider, and other pertinent information.

**Manner of Collection**

We collect your personal information as you sign up. We get information from our partners, particularly those you visit through the links found on our site and on links that direct to our site. We record information when you access our site and update your profile in our database. We use cookies in order to make browsing faster. Cookies are simple text files saved on your computer. Cookies remember your password, as well as the pages and links you visit. These are harmless. However, if you think we are violating your privacy, you can always remove these cookies by changing the settings of your browser.

We also use log files in collecting information. The information we collect using log files include:

  * Your internet protocol address
  * Searches you made within our site
  * Time spent on our site
  * The links you click
  * Device information while you are accessing our site on a mobile device
  * Browsing activity such as site crashes, browsing language, and browser type
  * Other non-personal information

**Reasons of Collecting Information**

We gather information in order for us to provide quality services to you and to all of our subscribers. We want to enhance your experience in navigating our website and improve some or all of our website’s features based on your reviews and suggestions.

**Use Of information**

Aside from using your personal information in enhancing our website, we may also use the information in cases of legal action against our company to protect our company’s legal rights. We may also share anonymous information, such as IP addresses, to the public and to our partners for purposes of demographic research.

**Security and Integrity**

We assure you that we do not share your personal information in purposes of selling or renting it to anyone without acquiring your consent. We work hard in creating security protocols so that your personal information is safe with us. The employees under the bearlike.com are bound to these same security protocols. No one is allowed full access to your personal information. Those who attempt to breach into our security will face consequences.

**Merger and Acquisition**

Even at the event of merger and acquisition, we maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. We do not divulge personal information without your consent. You can opt out as part of the transfer. In case you do not, we’ll notify you of our intention to transfer your personal information to the acquiring company. Once the transfer is complete, you are subjected to a new privacy policy that is not within our control. You take responsibility for reading and understanding the new policy.

**Changes**

Our company occasionally updates this privacy policy. So, please review these changes and leave us any comments (violent reactions are also more than welcome) before and after the implementation of changes. We notify you in case there are changes to the privacy policy. You’ll also be informed when the changes will finally be enforced.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
